They beam down. We rise up.
Z-O-M-B-I-E-S 3 is a fantasy, comedy, family film directed by Paul Hoen.
Zed and Addison are beginning their final year at Seabrook High in the town
that’s become a safe haven for monsters and humans alike.
Zed is anticipating an athletic scholarship that will make him the first Zombie to attend college,
while Addison is gearing up for Seabrook’s first international cheer-off competition.
Then suddenly, extraterrestrial beings appear around Seabrook,
provoking something other than friendly competition.
Addison, played by Meg Donnelly.
Zed, played by Milo Manheim.
Willa, played by Chandler Kinney.
Bucky, played by Trevor Tordjman.
Wyatt, played by Pearce Joza.
Wynter, played by Ariel Martin.
The film explores themes of high school, musical,
alien, high school graduation, zombie.
The tone is lighthearted.